var allQuestions = [{
    question: "Which sentence is correct?",
    option1: "I’ve been to Japan in 1989.",
    option2: "He’s been to Japan once.",
    option3: "He was in Japan since 1981.",
    option4: "I’ve been in Japan once.",
    answer: 2
  }, {
    question: "I _____ anyone so amusingly absent-minded.",
    option1: "could never known",
    option2: "have never known",
    option3: "never know",
    option4: "has never known",
    answer: 2
  }, {
    question: "If you’d written earlier, I’d have known when you _____ to go on holiday.",
    option1: "wanted",
    option2: "would intend",
    option3: "will want",
    option4: "would want",
    answer: 1
  },{
    question: "When _____ English?",
    option1: "has he begun to study",
    option2: " did he begin to study",
    option3: "did he begin study",
    option4: "has he begin study",
    answer: 2
  },{
    question: "As soon as she _____ in New York, she’ll ring us up.",
    option1: "would be",
    option2: "is",
    option3: "will be",
    option4: "was",
    answer: 2
  },{
    question: "Oil _____ on water.",
    option1: "is floating",
    option2: "used to float",
    option3: "floats",
    option4: "will float",
    answer: 3
  },{
    question: "They _____ to the cinema whenever they can.",
    option1: "have gone",
    option2: "go",
    option3: "would have gone",
    option4: "are going",
    answer: 2
  },{
    question: "She _____ cold. I’ll lend her my coat.",
    option1: "was looking",
    option2: "has been looking",
    option3: "is looking",
    option4: "looks",
    answer: 4
  },{
    question: "When the phone rang, she _____ a letter.",
    option1: "was writing",
    option2: "will write",
    option3: "has written",
    option4: "writes",
    answer: 1
  },{
    question: "I can’t call him now because I _____ his telephone number.",
    option1: "have lost",
    option2: "was lost",
    option3: "had lost",
    option4: "have been losing",
    answer: 1
  

}];